Nagarjun L



nagarjun2695@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/nagarjun2695



+39 3517871628



https://bit.ly/arjunpathy-portfolio

Summary

Experienced Web developer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry.

Skilled in Node.js, Amazon Web Services (AWS), ReactJs, AngularJS and JavaScript.

Have experience working with Ruby on Rails and Java (Spring Boot).

Built applications with responsive UI, microservice architectures and Oauth2 Services.

Experienced in both SQL and NoSQL databases.

I enjoy Foosball and Mobile Photography.

Experience



Full Stack Engineer

Codingmart Technologies

Jan 2017 - Feb 2019 (2 years 2 months)

Worked as a Full Stack Developer for Beam Ax - a cloud-based energy management system by

Mitsubishi Electric including graphical data representation and data management.

Created responsible and user-interactive webpages using angularis / Angular 2 and above, Javascript, HTML and CSS.

Served as a backend developer and created RESTful API endpoints using Node.js and RoR.

Worked on AWS lambdas, SNS, Cloud Watchers and EC2.

Developed a chatbot with Pub/Sub chat platform and NLP using Ruby on Rails.

Mentored junior developers on Javascript, Node.js and MongoDB

Full Stack Engineer

BetterPlace

Feb 2019 - Aug 2021 (2 years 7 months)

Built a stand-alone OAuth 2.0 authorisation system compatible with clients like web applications, mobile applications and APIs using Spring Boot.

Created responsible and user-interactive webpages using React Js, HTML and CSS.

Been instrumental in building various project's backend with secured RESTful APIs.

Written AWS lambdas for various event-driven data migrations helped seamless transition when we switched our old architecture to a new microservice architecture.

Written node scripts for various cross-platform bulk data migration with high efficiency and minimal error margin.

Education



Sapienza Università di Roma

Master of Science - MS, Computer Science 2021 - 2023

Sri Ramakrishna Engineering College

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information Technology 2013 - 2017



Bharathi Matriculation Higher Secondary School

Higher Secondary School

Skills

Node.js • JavaScript • Full-Stack Development • REST APIs • Problem Solving • Debugging • agile • MongoDB • React.js • Database Administration